http://www.wdtimes.com/site/privacy.html

Contests
Print Edition (to be discontinued soon; use E-Edition)
Site
PLEASE READ THE PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING WDTIMES.COM.By using this site, you signify your assent to these terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms of use, please do not use this site.PRIVACY POLICYWe believe you have a right to know what personal information is collected during your visits to the Watertown Daily Times website and how the information is used and safeguarded. You can view some of our content anonymously, but circumstances exist when information about you is collected. The information gathered falls into two categories: information you supply voluntarily and information we gather through technology.Information you supply voluntarilyTo use certain features and services on the Watertown Daily Times website, you may be asked to provide specific information about yourself. This information is collected when you fill out a browser-based form and is necessary to make the features useful and valuable. The forms have blank spaces into which you type the information. We collect information, including but not limited, your name, email address, telephone number, birth date and mailing address.How we use information you supply voluntarilyWe use the information you voluntarily supply to develop and offer content that best suits your interests, to complete transactions, or to communicate with you. For example, if you purchase a print subscription, we use your information to process your order. If you contact us for help, we use the information to contact you with a resolution to your problem or answer to your question. If you enter a contest, we use the information to determine eligibility and to contact winners.Information gathered through technologyTechnology helps us gather other information. Our web servers automatically collect information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, which is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet. You likely enter the Internet through your Internet service provider, your company or your school. Your IP address does not identify you personally. Your email address is not collected through this process, and no data on your hard drive or personal or institutional servers are read.We also collect aggregate information on how many people visit our sites and what pages people access on our sites. Some of this information is gathered using a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie." A cookie cannot read data on your hard drive or server or gather other personal information about you such as your name or email address. Aggregate information is processed by third party services: Omniture and Google Analytics.Return/Refund PolicySubscriptions: Newspaper subscriptions delivered by Carrier, U.S. Mail or available as an E-edition online. All subscriptions to the newspapers are paid in advance and entitled to a refund for the unused portion of the year if the newspaper is cancelled. A refund will be based on the pro-rated weeks remaining in the subscription. Refunds for payments made by credit card will be made to the credit card.
Trending Now
Ryan N. Schmidt
Wayne F. Schliewe
Danny Short
High-speed chase in Creek ends in Fort
Dozens of improvements helping boost downtown in midst of pandemic
Newsletters
Obituaries newsletterReceive a daily list of obituaries in your inbox
SUBSCRIBE NOW!
Latest e-Edition
Watertown's Daily Times
To view our latest e-Edition click the image on the left.
© Copyright 2020 Watertown Daily Times Online, 218 S. First St. Watertown, WI | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
